[{"answer": "An informant", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " It was an anonymous tip", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't know.  Something", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Inhale the smoke and hold it", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Not like.  It is", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "He didn't hang around us.  He's like one of those hippie kids.  I'm not part of that group.  It was a party in all these rooms.  His girlfriend who I barely know was completely hysterical... He's blue, he's puking... We didn't want to get in trouble, but what were we supposed to do?  I mean, what would you have done if you had been us", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He's a friend.  He's also like the only one who was dealing with the situation.  He'd definitely had a few beers, but it's not like he wanted to drive.  We didn't know what else to do.  It wasn't my pot", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "One thing bothers me...  That kid they dropped off had coke and heroin in him.  Serious amounts.  He's lucky he lived.  So I gotta as", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I mean, did you ask her?  What kind of drugs has she tried", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Who", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Your new friends", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I got greedy.  I decided to bring a little in on my own and somebody tipped you off.  That was my mistake. my friend would never be so stupid", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend and I were friends from childhood.  He was loyal, that's not a mistake", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I have a drink before dinner to take the edge off my day.  That's different", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yeah, because the alternative is to be bored to death", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "How's my friend", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh, man", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I tried to talk to her when she was up there, but they wouldn't put me through.  I'm surprised she hasn't called", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm six months pregnant.  I won't do it", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Fine, then we don't have a deal", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend, do think there's a difference between a reason and an excuse, because I don't think there is", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Goodbye my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hello, my friend.  What a great party", "docId": "traffic.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Nobody.  I'm a nobody who arrested you, but your wife is a murderer", "qsentId": 26}]